<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Care Frontiers Podcast By unnus on unnus </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Care Frontiers Podcast By unnus on unnus </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/podcast/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Care Frontiers Season One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/all/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/all/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advantages of business coaching in healthcare with Dr. Janice Hughes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-coaching/</guid>
      <description>Janice:&#xA;It was when I had a coach, a more business minded coach, that I was able to put some systems and policies and procedures in place that not only did it aid the practice, I want people listening to understand it increased the value of the practice.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome to the Care Frontiers podcast, the show where we interview thought leaders in healthcare to share with us their expert knowledge and business branding and marketing if you&amp;rsquo;re a pracitioner or medical business owner or an executive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brand Building In Healthcare With Dr. Ryan Rieder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/medical-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/medical-branding/</guid>
      <description>Ryan:&#xA;We all like to believe that being the best at the thing correlates with us being the top earner in the industry. Now, if you look traditionally at the top 1% of earners in any expert space very seldom that the top 1% earners correlate with being the best at the thing. they&amp;rsquo;re not. They&amp;rsquo;re the best at the marketing and the branding and positioning of the thing.&#xA;Sliman:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branding And Business Positioning In Healthcare With Susan Meier</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-positioning-and-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-positioning-and-branding/</guid>
      <description>Susan:&#xA;So while it feels like, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re a small business owner, it can feel terrifying the idea of turning down work. But you have to remember that the space that you create by not taking the wrong work is space that you open up for taking the right work. And that&amp;rsquo;s actually what&amp;rsquo;s going to make your business grow.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the Care Frontiers podcast, the show where we bring healthcare professionals to share with us their own experience running a successful medical business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building brand culture of trust with Dr. Steven Rasner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/patient-trust-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/patient-trust-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Steven:&#xA;Do I want to stop seeing 25 patients a day running room to room doing great volume? And that&amp;rsquo;s how I make my living with very unfulfilling day after day or do I want to develop a relationship based practice where people actually come to me because they truly love you.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome to the care frontier podcast The show where we interview thought leaders in health care to share with us their expert knowledge in everything business, branding, and marketing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building The Ultimate Patient Experience With Dr. David Moffet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/ultimate-patient-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/ultimate-patient-experience/</guid>
      <description>David:&#xA;They can&amp;rsquo;t just stay where they are because staying where you are is actually going backwards because everybody else is moving forward, like a running race. You stop, everybody goes past you. And so you&amp;rsquo;ve got to be in motion. You&amp;rsquo;ve got to be moving.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the care frontiers podcast The show where we bring healthcare professionals to share with us their own experience running a successful medical business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutting Healthcare Business Expenses With Dr. Josh Luke</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-expenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-expenses/</guid>
      <description>Josh:&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;d be amazed how many times people are like &amp;ldquo;I want to sell to hospitals&amp;rdquo;. Why would the hospital buy anything? They&amp;rsquo;re just an expense in the model now. &amp;ldquo;oh we have this great technology then for health plans and health systems that they&amp;rsquo;re going to love&amp;rdquo;. Well, they&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this model for 20 years. What about your approach is new? just because you came from the acute space, it&amp;rsquo;s just new to you, it may not be new to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Entrepreneurship With Dr. Ernesto Gutierrez </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-entrepreneurship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-entrepreneurship/</guid>
      <description>Ernesto:&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;re indoctrinating your patients, you&amp;rsquo;re literally whispering in their ear about your products and your processes. And these are people who are already interested in them. The moment that they set foot in your office and you have never met them, they already know you, because you&amp;rsquo;ve been talking to them.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome to the Care Frontiers podcast The show where we interview thought leaders in healthcare to share with us their expert knowledge and business branding and marketing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Inbound Marketing With Alex Membrillo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-inbound-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-inbound-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Alex:&#xA;For the majority of medical practice out there, they just need to be all over Google. They don&amp;rsquo;t need to be worrying about social media because SEO is where people are going and actually looking for care. Social media is where people are talking about things. And they&amp;rsquo;re really not talking to companies like you anyways, you know, they don&amp;rsquo;t talk to healthcare groups.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the Care Frontiers podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare SEO Marketing With Codrin Arsene </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-seo/</guid>
      <description>Codrin:&#xA;Any type of healthcare company that really wants to get in front of the largest amount of people who may be interested in their services should consider investing in SEO.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the Care Frontiers podcast. The show where we bring healthcare professionals to share with us their own experience running a successful medical business. Joining me today the CEO of Digital Authority Partners and the healthcare weekly digital magazine Codrin Arsene, Codrin, welcome to our show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increase Your Case Acceptance With Dr. Christopher Phelps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/increase-case-acceptance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/increase-case-acceptance/</guid>
      <description>Chris:&#xA;Whether you realize it or not, when a patient walks in the door, your practice when you&amp;rsquo;re speaking to them on the telephone for the first time, whatever the situation is, right? They&amp;rsquo;re coming into that situation with a mindset already pre established. And if you don&amp;rsquo;t do anything to change that mindset, the odds are pretty good, that, their mindset wherever it&amp;rsquo;s at is not here focused on their health need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Branding For Doctors With Dr. Gary Wortz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/personal-branding-for-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/personal-branding-for-doctors/</guid>
      <description>Gary:&#xA;Understanding the message that you have to share and trying to stay on message and on brand can really help you find your niche. You know, growing your brand is not about being all things to all people. It&amp;rsquo;s about being an expert to a very small group of people who are passionate and share the same passions that you have.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen, to the Care Frontiers podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media marketing in dentistry with Dr. Tiffani Long</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Tiffani:&#xA;People are getting to know you, people are looking at your videos, your stories and your photos and they&amp;rsquo;re already liking you before they even come in to see you.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Hello and welcome to the Care Frontiers podcast today, we have a very special guest with me, Dr. Tiffani Long. Dr. Tiffani is the owner of Epic Dental Arts Practice. The practice is located in Oregon Forest Groove. Albeit not a very good year, 2020 marks the 20th year anniversary for Dr.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
