<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unnus </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/private/</link>
    <description>Recent content on unnus </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/private/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Brand your medical business</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/brand-intensive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/brand-intensive/</guid>
      <description>how much of business growth are you missing out on by not&amp;nbsp; implementing these strategies? By really focusing on differentiating your practice, you provide a value beyond your care services.&#xA;The next question you needs to answer is:&#xA;What are the practical steps to take in order to expand and build my healthcare brand?&#xA;We’d like to introduce you to our Healthcare Brand Intensive Service here’s how it works:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, successful order</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/success/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, You&#39;re almost there</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/acknowledgment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/acknowledgment/</guid>
      <description> Get closer to us Free Products Healthcare Strategies Free Healthcare Course Useful Resources Hospital Branding Healthcare Strategies Marketing for healthcare Strategies for clinical growth Quick Links Contact About Work Social Twitter Facebook Instagram </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unnus | Healthcare Branding Agency</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/formerHomepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/formerHomepage/</guid>
      <description>How effectively can you operate in an environment that has multiple care facilities competing for the same patients and services? Giving the flood of “me too” care services, patients have wider options to pick and choose from&#xA;Ironically, when medical businesses are faced with competition from too many services, features, messages, meanings, or media, their first reaction is to fight clutter with more clutter.&#xA;It&#39;s like trying to put out a fire with gasoline</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
