<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unnus | Healthcare Branding Agency on unnus </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in unnus | Healthcare Branding Agency on unnus </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re helping The Purveyors Of Modern Miracles unnus is a fully-remote healthcare branding agency aiming to set your medical brand for success and to drive growth, build awareness and create uniquness for your business, all through creative design thinking&#xA;We&#39;re healthcare focused Unlike most ad agencies, our approach is healthcare-focused.&#xA;With strategic profiling, we establish your healthcare business and set it apart from the rest.&#xA;We strive to help you to find a &#34;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact us | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Care Frontiers Season One</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/all/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2020 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/all/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Press | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/press/</guid>
      <description>Appropriate Logo Usage Feel free to leverage any of the unnus brand materials to refer to unnus and its brand. However, we ask that the logo and mark be displayed in a proportionate and simple manner on either a dark or light background.&#xA;Download Logotypes Spelling “unnus” Our name should always be displayed as “unnus” on any and all branding materials. Please do not write the name as “Unnus,” “UNNUS” or in any other way that violates our naming standards.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Charismatic Medical Brand | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/charismatic-medical-brand/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/charismatic-medical-brand/</guid>
      <description>1) You&#39;ll see how to craft the unmatched advantage of being purposeful medical business People have a cognitive bias towards meaningful brands. Brands that are purpose-driven and possess a high sense of mission. We vouch for their success, we stay loyal and spread the gospel about them. That’s because they reflect our beliefs and reinforce our core characteristics.&#xA;In the first lesson, we’ll go through how you’ll infuse a dash of “meaningful substance” to your medical business and how that will lead you to attract cult-like followings and a loyal patient base.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Four Dollar UX | The internet’s most affordable UX Report - unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/four-dollar-ux/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/four-dollar-ux/</guid>
      <description>How It Works What&#39;s Inside? 1) A complete Rundown of your user experience User experience (UX) focuses on having a deep understanding of users, what they need, what they value, their abilities, and also their limitations. By buying our report, you&#39;ll get a comprhansive rundown of your page&#39;s UX and how to improve each and every aspect of it. 2) Comprhensive PDF report + Action-steps Our team will prepare a compact PDF report that contains design issues, action plans, and expert advice on how to solve them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Re;Branded Project | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rebranded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rebranded/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rehab Marketing: A New Gimmicks-Free Guide [2024]&#43; Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/rehab-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/rehab-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Tired of rehab marketing that&amp;rsquo;s all flash and no substance? It&amp;rsquo;s time to get sober and ditch the gimmicks.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Your Practice: 25 Patient Management Softwares [2024] </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/patient-software-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/patient-software-management/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  You’re probably tired of drowning in paperwork and administrative tasks. Today you’ll discover 21 solutions catered to your practice.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Video Marketing is influencing the future of Healthcare</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-video-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-video-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Video marketing is powerful. It&amp;rsquo;s effective. And yes, it&amp;rsquo;s result-oriented too.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>22 Absolutely Jaw-Dropping Dental Websites For 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/best-dental-websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/best-dental-websites/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  If you’re bored with the same “lookalike” dental sites, we are too. Let’s check some of the most creative dental websites.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>95 Dental Facts And Statistics For 2024 [&#43; Visuals]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/dental-facts-statistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/dental-facts-statistics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Are you looking for “jaw-dropping” facts and statistics regarding dentistry in 2021? Look no further.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>65 Chiropractic Facts And Statistics For 2024 [NEW]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/chiropractic-facts-statistics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/chiropractic-facts-statistics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Today’s you’ll learn about spine-chilling figures and facts regarding chiropractic care in 2021.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How To Grow Your Medical Practice (And Patient Volume) 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/how-to-grow-medical-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/how-to-grow-medical-practice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Today, I&amp;rsquo;ll share with you battle-tested tips that’ll help you reignite your practice’s growth and catapult it out of the plateau phase.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 1) Brand DNA Workshop: How to infuse meaning to your medical brand </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-dna/</guid>
      <description>“People don&amp;rsquo;t buy what you do; they buy why you do it. And what you do simply proves what you believe”—Simon Sinek The above quote holds the theme of this first lesson. People don’t care about any brand, but what they care about is the purposeful endeavor of said brand.&#xA;We have a cognitive bias towards meaningful brands. We vouch for their success, we stay loyal and spread the gospel about them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 2) Brand Positioning Workshop: Differentiating your medical brand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-positioning/</guid>
      <description>In an age where the patient choice is expanding rapidly, where people are time-poor and information-rich; Where everyone is fist-fighting for your patient’s short attention, not differentiating your medical business is the same as being invisible. For the first time in history, competition does not come from your direct competitors, indeed, but from the market clutter.&#xA;According to research done by the Red Crown Marketing agency, It is estimated that the average person encounters between 6,000 to 10,000 ads daily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 3) Brand Persona Workshop: Humanizing Your Medical Brand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-persona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-persona/</guid>
      <description>Today, people are not just choosing the best, the fanciest, or the cheapest. They’re choosing brands that have the right meaning. In the supermarkets, consumers are choosing to pay twice as much for eggs from humanely-treated cage-free chickens because of their values, not because it’s a better egg.&#xA;They do this because they don’t want to be the cause of any mistreatment of chickens (caged birds with their beaks clipped and all that).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 4) Brand Storytelling: A Framework to Attract And Captivate your audience&#39;s hearts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-storytelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-storytelling/</guid>
      <description>Imagine what you want to say to your patient goes through intact - crystal clear and potent? What if your messages are perceived straight into people&amp;rsquo;s brains without distortion, noise, or the need to think too much about it? Well-told stories sell. why? Because they can go where quantitative analysis is denied admission: our hearts. Data can persuade people, but it doesn’t inspire them to act.&#xA;And today, we’re going to use Brand Storytelling to shrink the &amp;ldquo;psychic distance” between your medical business and your ideal patient so that a relationship can begin to develop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 5): Brand Art Direction: How To Craft A Mesmerizing Brand Visuals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-identity/</guid>
      <description>Your visuals can turn your medical business into a premium brand. And the reason for that is because of how our brain interprets visual elements. We are visual beings and we’re biased towards what is visually appealing and aesthetically meaningful. Our brains are wired to react to things that have meaning before they construct the perceptions of objects.&#xA;This means, you perceive the meaning of things then, and only then, you see the visual elements of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 6) How to Measure Your Branding ROI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-roi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-roi/</guid>
      <description>Healthcare brands are now obsessed with patient acquisitions, ROI, revenues, and colorful charts. But if we’d like to build sustainable medical brands, we should reroute our attention to more dependable measurement units. Your revenue might not be the best metric to keep an eye on&amp;hellip; In the business world, often the focus is on yearly revenue or sales. Not only that, but marketers, to measure their marketing efforts, need to project the sales each quarter.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Marketing: The Definitive Guide (2024) </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  If you’re looking to market your medical business, you’re in luck. This guide will be so valuable you’ll make hard copies out of it and hide them in multiple off-site locations.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clinic Names: How to Craft A Buzzworthy Practice Name &#43;Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/clinic-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Mar 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/clinic-names/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  It’s an ironic fact that your medical brand’s most valuable asset is often the one given the least attention—its name.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Maybe because people aren’t aware of the widening costs of a poorly named brand, or the streamlining effects of a well-named one.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Journey Mapping In 2024, Guide &#43; [Examples &amp; Template]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/patient-journey-mapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/patient-journey-mapping/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Patient Journey Maps are the secret ingredient to a thriving medical business. Let’s discuss how to implement this strategy for your practice in under 3 days.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proven Nursing Home Marketing Ideas &#43; (Traps to Avoid) [2024]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/nursing-home-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/nursing-home-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  If you’re looking for a resilient way to market your nursing home facility, Look no further. This article contains proven marketing strategies for senior living facilities.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Audiology Marketing: Powerful ways to Market Your Practice 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/audiology-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/audiology-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  Due to the commoditization of hearing aids, You might find it hard to attract patients and sell your care services. Let’s solve that.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New (And Foolproof) Marketing Strategies For Doctors (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/marketing-for-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/marketing-for-doctors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  This article outlines proven and strategic ways to catapult your practice profitability to the next level.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>New (And Powerful) Medical Device Marketing Strategies (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/medical-device-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/medical-device-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;Outdated medical device marketing is out of sync with the rapidly changing MedTech industry. This article outlines a new and effective approach.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Strategic Planning In Healthcare: 2024 Guide &#43; Examples</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-strategic-planning/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-strategic-planning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  This guide contains new healthcare planning strategies, their benefits, examples, traps to avoid, and all you need to know.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little-Known Chiropractic Marketing Ideas 2024 [&#43;Examples]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/chiropractic-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Dec 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/chiropractic-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;TLDR: I’ll share with you unconventional but ridiculously powerful chiropractic marketing strategies. I’ll also cover common pitfalls to avoid when marketing your practice.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospice Marketing: New Strategies (&#43; Mistakes To Avoid) 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/hospice-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/hospice-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;Looking to increase your referral rates for your agency? Or a new marketing strategy for your hospice? This article is for you.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 Awe-Inducing Healthcare Advertising Campaigns [&#43;Videos]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-advertising/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-advertising/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;Warning: This list contain ads that may tug your heartstrings, uplift your mood, or tickle your stomach.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Step-By-Step Guide To SWOT Analysis In Healthcare [2024]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-swot-analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-swot-analysis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  In this article, I’ll share with you what is SWOT Analysis, how you can perform it, AND how you can &lt;em&gt;track&lt;/em&gt; your success using this tool.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Little-known Orthodontic Marketing Ideas 2023 (&#43;Examples)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/orthodontic-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/orthodontic-marketing/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for ways to market your orthodontic practice, Look no further. I’ll share with you creative marketing tips on how to create a profitable and future-proof orthodontic brand&lt;/strong&gt;.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Branding: The Definitive Guide [2024] </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-branding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  As the pace of healthcare quickens and the number of brands multiplies, it’s patients, not medical businesses, who decide which brands live and which ones die.&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pharma Branding: Create A Market-Leading Company (2024)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/pharma-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/pharma-branding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;The rate at which competition is surging in Big Pharma is quickening.&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;How do you break through the noise and single your company out?&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>29 Unique Healthcare Mission Statements: 2024 [Examples]</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-mission-statement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/healthcare-mission-statement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;There’s no shortage of the same sounding mission statements.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;Healthcare brands use them as a “decoration”.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;But a mission statement carries with them unexplored advantages.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dental Branding: The Anatomy Of A Mouth-Watering Dental Practice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/dental-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/dental-branding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;You want your patients to fall head-over-heels in love with your practice?&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;The Best way of achieving that is to build a charismatic dental brand.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patient Engagement: A Practical Guide (Free Tool &#43; Planners)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/patient-engagement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/patient-engagement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&#xA;  &lt;strong&gt;This isn&amp;rsquo;t your typical snooze-fest lecture; it&amp;rsquo;s a practical step-by-step map to turning any clinic from meh to memorable.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hospital Branding: How to Build A Timeless Hospital Brand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/medical/hospital-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/medical/hospital-branding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;section  id=&#34;Intro&#34;&gt; &lt;div class=&#34;hook&#34;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s terrifying research. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to recent study by deloitte, 50% of the current hospital systems will not exist in the next 10 years. Meaning, mediocre hospitals are to drop like flies in the following decade.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;hr&gt; &lt;/div&gt; &lt;p&gt;You see, that’s not surprising in the slightest.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advantages of business coaching in healthcare with Dr. Janice Hughes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-coaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-coaching/</guid>
      <description>Janice:&#xA;It was when I had a coach, a more business minded coach, that I was able to put some systems and policies and procedures in place that not only did it aid the practice, I want people listening to understand it increased the value of the practice.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome to the Care Frontiers podcast, the show where we interview thought leaders in healthcare to share with us their expert knowledge and business branding and marketing if you&amp;rsquo;re a pracitioner or medical business owner or an executive.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brand Building In Healthcare With Dr. Ryan Rieder</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/medical-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/medical-branding/</guid>
      <description>Ryan:&#xA;We all like to believe that being the best at the thing correlates with us being the top earner in the industry. Now, if you look traditionally at the top 1% of earners in any expert space very seldom that the top 1% earners correlate with being the best at the thing. they&amp;rsquo;re not. They&amp;rsquo;re the best at the marketing and the branding and positioning of the thing.&#xA;Sliman:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brand your medical business</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/brand-intensive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/brand-intensive/</guid>
      <description>how much of business growth are you missing out on by not&amp;nbsp; implementing these strategies? By really focusing on differentiating your practice, you provide a value beyond your care services.&#xA;The next question you needs to answer is:&#xA;What are the practical steps to take in order to expand and build my healthcare brand?&#xA;We’d like to introduce you to our Healthcare Brand Intensive Service here’s how it works:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Branding And Business Positioning In Healthcare With Susan Meier</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-positioning-and-branding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-positioning-and-branding/</guid>
      <description>Susan:&#xA;So while it feels like, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re a small business owner, it can feel terrifying the idea of turning down work. But you have to remember that the space that you create by not taking the wrong work is space that you open up for taking the right work. And that&amp;rsquo;s actually what&amp;rsquo;s going to make your business grow.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the Care Frontiers podcast, the show where we bring healthcare professionals to share with us their own experience running a successful medical business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building brand culture of trust with Dr. Steven Rasner</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/patient-trust-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/patient-trust-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Steven:&#xA;Do I want to stop seeing 25 patients a day running room to room doing great volume? And that&amp;rsquo;s how I make my living with very unfulfilling day after day or do I want to develop a relationship based practice where people actually come to me because they truly love you.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome to the care frontier podcast The show where we interview thought leaders in health care to share with us their expert knowledge in everything business, branding, and marketing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building The Ultimate Patient Experience With Dr. David Moffet</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/ultimate-patient-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/ultimate-patient-experience/</guid>
      <description>David:&#xA;They can&amp;rsquo;t just stay where they are because staying where you are is actually going backwards because everybody else is moving forward, like a running race. You stop, everybody goes past you. And so you&amp;rsquo;ve got to be in motion. You&amp;rsquo;ve got to be moving.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the care frontiers podcast The show where we bring healthcare professionals to share with us their own experience running a successful medical business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>case study caresect | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/caresect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/caresect/</guid>
      <description>How can a fairly new clinic break through the noise of an already saturated market? Being new and fresh, caresect needed something to single them out of the crowd. patients sought more established centers and institutions&#xA;unnus managed to make caresect&#39;s freshness and newness its most powerful element.&#xA;Work done Branding Identity Website Brand Guideline Book Starting from the ground up.&#xA;Brand Strategy, Creative Design, Typeface, Color, Mobile, Website. a place of wellbeing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>case study healthier | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/healthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/healthier/</guid>
      <description>New Start, New Identity After countless resources healthier spent on its visual identity, faced the underlining problem: their visuals doesn&#39;t reflect their internal brand.&#xA;I took a different route to healthier&#39;s identity by implementing a strategic design process to create a more representative aesthetics&#xA;Work done Identity Re-brand New UI Design New Website Design Ruby&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Green&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Green&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Green&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Memorable patient experience, from all devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>case study rodbell | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/rodbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/rodbell/</guid>
      <description>Why compete if you can&#xA;create brand new market? Despite the cutthroat market Rodbell found itself in, the team at unnus developed compact differentation strategy aimed to put rodbell in a brand new market space&#xA;Rodbell radically shifted its positioning to more of a holistic way of branding itself in the pharma industry, resulting in building special attribuites, no competitor are able to imitate Work done Brand Awareness Strategic planning Website and digital collaterals TODAY&#39;S TOMORROW</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cutting Healthcare Business Expenses With Dr. Josh Luke</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-expenses/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-business-expenses/</guid>
      <description>Josh:&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;d be amazed how many times people are like &amp;ldquo;I want to sell to hospitals&amp;rdquo;. Why would the hospital buy anything? They&amp;rsquo;re just an expense in the model now. &amp;ldquo;oh we have this great technology then for health plans and health systems that they&amp;rsquo;re going to love&amp;rdquo;. Well, they&amp;rsquo;ve been doing this model for 20 years. What about your approach is new? just because you came from the acute space, it&amp;rsquo;s just new to you, it may not be new to them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Entrepreneurship With Dr. Ernesto Gutierrez </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-entrepreneurship/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-entrepreneurship/</guid>
      <description>Ernesto:&#xA;You&amp;rsquo;re indoctrinating your patients, you&amp;rsquo;re literally whispering in their ear about your products and your processes. And these are people who are already interested in them. The moment that they set foot in your office and you have never met them, they already know you, because you&amp;rsquo;ve been talking to them.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome to the Care Frontiers podcast The show where we interview thought leaders in healthcare to share with us their expert knowledge and business branding and marketing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare Inbound Marketing With Alex Membrillo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-inbound-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-inbound-marketing/</guid>
      <description>Alex:&#xA;For the majority of medical practice out there, they just need to be all over Google. They don&amp;rsquo;t need to be worrying about social media because SEO is where people are going and actually looking for care. Social media is where people are talking about things. And they&amp;rsquo;re really not talking to companies like you anyways, you know, they don&amp;rsquo;t talk to healthcare groups.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the Care Frontiers podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare SEO Marketing With Codrin Arsene </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-seo/</guid>
      <description>Codrin:&#xA;Any type of healthcare company that really wants to get in front of the largest amount of people who may be interested in their services should consider investing in SEO.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen to the Care Frontiers podcast. The show where we bring healthcare professionals to share with us their own experience running a successful medical business. Joining me today the CEO of Digital Authority Partners and the healthcare weekly digital magazine Codrin Arsene, Codrin, welcome to our show.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Increase Your Case Acceptance With Dr. Christopher Phelps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/increase-case-acceptance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/increase-case-acceptance/</guid>
      <description>Chris:&#xA;Whether you realize it or not, when a patient walks in the door, your practice when you&amp;rsquo;re speaking to them on the telephone for the first time, whatever the situation is, right? They&amp;rsquo;re coming into that situation with a mindset already pre established. And if you don&amp;rsquo;t do anything to change that mindset, the odds are pretty good, that, their mindset wherever it&amp;rsquo;s at is not here focused on their health need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Personal Branding For Doctors With Dr. Gary Wortz</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/personal-branding-for-doctors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/personal-branding-for-doctors/</guid>
      <description>Gary:&#xA;Understanding the message that you have to share and trying to stay on message and on brand can really help you find your niche. You know, growing your brand is not about being all things to all people. It&amp;rsquo;s about being an expert to a very small group of people who are passionate and share the same passions that you have.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Welcome back, ladies and gentlemen, to the Care Frontiers podcast.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social media marketing in dentistry with Dr. Tiffani Long</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-social-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/podcast/season-one/healthcare-social-media/</guid>
      <description>Tiffani:&#xA;People are getting to know you, people are looking at your videos, your stories and your photos and they&amp;rsquo;re already liking you before they even come in to see you.&#xA;Sliman:&#xA;Hello and welcome to the Care Frontiers podcast today, we have a very special guest with me, Dr. Tiffani Long. Dr. Tiffani is the owner of Epic Dental Arts Practice. The practice is located in Oregon Forest Groove. Albeit not a very good year, 2020 marks the 20th year anniversary for Dr.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, successful order</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/success/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, You&#39;re almost there</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/acknowledgment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/acknowledgment/</guid>
      <description> Get closer to us Free Products Healthcare Strategies Free Healthcare Course Useful Resources Hospital Branding Healthcare Strategies Marketing for healthcare Strategies for clinical growth Quick Links Contact About Work Social Twitter Facebook Instagram </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>unnus | Healthcare Branding Agency</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/private/formerHomepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/private/formerHomepage/</guid>
      <description>How effectively can you operate in an environment that has multiple care facilities competing for the same patients and services? Giving the flood of “me too” care services, patients have wider options to pick and choose from&#xA;Ironically, when medical businesses are faced with competition from too many services, features, messages, meanings, or media, their first reaction is to fight clutter with more clutter.&#xA;It&#39;s like trying to put out a fire with gasoline</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
