<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unnus </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/</link>
    <description>Recent content on unnus </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/case-studies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>case study caresect | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/caresect/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/caresect/</guid>
      <description>How can a fairly new clinic break through the noise of an already saturated market? Being new and fresh, caresect needed something to single them out of the crowd. patients sought more established centers and institutions&#xA;unnus managed to make caresect&#39;s freshness and newness its most powerful element.&#xA;Work done Branding Identity Website Brand Guideline Book Starting from the ground up.&#xA;Brand Strategy, Creative Design, Typeface, Color, Mobile, Website. a place of wellbeing</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>case study healthier | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/healthier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/healthier/</guid>
      <description>New Start, New Identity After countless resources healthier spent on its visual identity, faced the underlining problem: their visuals doesn&#39;t reflect their internal brand.&#xA;I took a different route to healthier&#39;s identity by implementing a strategic design process to create a more representative aesthetics&#xA;Work done Identity Re-brand New UI Design New Website Design Ruby&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Green&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Green&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Green&#xA;#D8334A&#xA;rgb(216,51,74)&#xA;Memorable patient experience, from all devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>case study rodbell | unnus</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/rodbell/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/case-studies/rodbell/</guid>
      <description>Why compete if you can&#xA;create brand new market? Despite the cutthroat market Rodbell found itself in, the team at unnus developed compact differentation strategy aimed to put rodbell in a brand new market space&#xA;Rodbell radically shifted its positioning to more of a holistic way of branding itself in the pharma industry, resulting in building special attribuites, no competitor are able to imitate Work done Brand Awareness Strategic planning Website and digital collaterals TODAY&#39;S TOMORROW</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
