<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>unnus </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/email/</link>
    <description>Recent content on unnus </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/email/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 1) Brand DNA Workshop: How to infuse meaning to your medical brand </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-dna/</guid>
      <description>“People don&amp;rsquo;t buy what you do; they buy why you do it. And what you do simply proves what you believe”—Simon Sinek The above quote holds the theme of this first lesson. People don’t care about any brand, but what they care about is the purposeful endeavor of said brand.&#xA;We have a cognitive bias towards meaningful brands. We vouch for their success, we stay loyal and spread the gospel about them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 2) Brand Positioning Workshop: Differentiating your medical brand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-positioning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-positioning/</guid>
      <description>In an age where the patient choice is expanding rapidly, where people are time-poor and information-rich; Where everyone is fist-fighting for your patient’s short attention, not differentiating your medical business is the same as being invisible. For the first time in history, competition does not come from your direct competitors, indeed, but from the market clutter.&#xA;According to research done by the Red Crown Marketing agency, It is estimated that the average person encounters between 6,000 to 10,000 ads daily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 3) Brand Persona Workshop: Humanizing Your Medical Brand</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-persona/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-persona/</guid>
      <description>Today, people are not just choosing the best, the fanciest, or the cheapest. They’re choosing brands that have the right meaning. In the supermarkets, consumers are choosing to pay twice as much for eggs from humanely-treated cage-free chickens because of their values, not because it’s a better egg.&#xA;They do this because they don’t want to be the cause of any mistreatment of chickens (caged birds with their beaks clipped and all that).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 4) Brand Storytelling: A Framework to Attract And Captivate your audience&#39;s hearts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-storytelling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-storytelling/</guid>
      <description>Imagine what you want to say to your patient goes through intact - crystal clear and potent? What if your messages are perceived straight into people&amp;rsquo;s brains without distortion, noise, or the need to think too much about it? Well-told stories sell. why? Because they can go where quantitative analysis is denied admission: our hearts. Data can persuade people, but it doesn’t inspire them to act.&#xA;And today, we’re going to use Brand Storytelling to shrink the &amp;ldquo;psychic distance” between your medical business and your ideal patient so that a relationship can begin to develop.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 5): Brand Art Direction: How To Craft A Mesmerizing Brand Visuals</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-identity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-identity/</guid>
      <description>Your visuals can turn your medical business into a premium brand. And the reason for that is because of how our brain interprets visual elements. We are visual beings and we’re biased towards what is visually appealing and aesthetically meaningful. Our brains are wired to react to things that have meaning before they construct the perceptions of objects.&#xA;This means, you perceive the meaning of things then, and only then, you see the visual elements of it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lesson 6) How to Measure Your Branding ROI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-roi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/email/brand-roi/</guid>
      <description>Healthcare brands are now obsessed with patient acquisitions, ROI, revenues, and colorful charts. But if we’d like to build sustainable medical brands, we should reroute our attention to more dependable measurement units. Your revenue might not be the best metric to keep an eye on&amp;hellip; In the business world, often the focus is on yearly revenue or sales. Not only that, but marketers, to measure their marketing efforts, need to project the sales each quarter.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
